<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Email Template for Inquies about Cleaning the Panels</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>Partner_Template</letterhead>
    <name>Customer Service: Email Template for Inquies about Cleaning the Panels</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>SunPower – The Most Powerful Solar: Web Inquiry Response</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Lead.Name},


Thank you for your interest in SunPower, The World’s Standard for Solar.

Under most circumstances, panels will never need cleaning. Seasonal rains should be adequate for clearing most soiling. If severe soiling occurs, you can clean the
panels by spraying them from the ground with a standard garden hose. SunPower
strongly recommends that homeowners only clean panels in the early morning or
late evening rather than when the sun is at its peak or when the panels are
warm. 

 

General Safety Precautions:
      
Do not clean the panels during the middle of the day. To avoid panel damage, allow
the panels to cool before cleaning.     
Do not use abrasive cleaners or anything that could scratch the surface of the
panels.
Do not attempt to access the roof for panel cleaning or inspection.
   
For hard-to-remove debris, consider the following solutions:

For Anti Reflective Coating (ARC) glass:

Various glass cleaners, including Windex have been tested on ARC glass, so we can consider glass cleaners safe to be used as a cleaning solution as long as it the cleaner is not applied with an abrasive sponge that will induce scratches (such as Scotch Brite). Kitchen dish soap is also acceptable. Take care that the glass is rinsed well such that no residue is left (aesthetic issue).


For regular, non-ARC glass: use any off-the-shelf glass cleaner:

If paint overspray has occurred on the module glass, then escalate to Applications Engineering for further evaluation. For non-ARC glass, we recommend that IPA (Isopropyl alcohol) be used, but contact with the frame-to-glass gasket should be kept to a minimum.


WARNING:
Spraying cold water on a hot panel could result in panel damage and void your
warranty.

For more information about SunPower products, you may visit our website www.sunpowercorp.com or call our Customer Care line at 1-800-SUNPOWER
(1-800-786-7693).



Regards, 

{!Lead.OwnerFirstName}
SunPower Customer Care Team 
www.sunpowercorp.com 
1-800-SUNPOWER







 </textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
