<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Used for leads where no dealers are opted-in to lead flow</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>StandardLetterhead</letterhead>
    <name>Meet the SPWR Partners in your Area</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>{!Lead.FirstName}, meet the SunPower Partners in your area!</subject>
    <textOnly>MEET THE SUNPOWER PARTNERS IN YOUR AREA
{!Lead.FirstName} {!Lead.LastName}, {!Lead.Street}, {!Lead.StateCode}
{!Lead.Phone}; Current Average Bill: {!Lead.Average_Monthly_Electricity_Bill__c}

Hello {!Lead.Average_Monthly_Electricity_Bill__c},


We’re so glad that you’re interested in learning more about our powerful, efficient, reliable home solar solutions. We know making the right choice for your home is extremely important, and we know you have questions.


Below is a list of the SunPower Partners that serve your area, along with information for contacting.  SunPower takes pride in working with Partners who are committed to creating solutions for the unique needs of our customers.  These Partners are ready to help you go solar with SunPower panels. As a next step, we encourage you to reach out to these dealers directly to learn more.





&lt;&lt;NAMES OF THE DEALERS THAT SERVE THE CUSTOMER’S ZIP CODE, based on the Dealer Locator&gt;&gt;



When making a decision about solar, there are a few key things to keep in mind:

· Preparing for your meeting: Gather as many of your electric bills as you can from the past 12 months. This will help to accurately calculate your current usage.


· Don’t have your old bills handy? Don’t worry, most utilities allow you to download the previous year’s bill.


· How dependable is the company behind the panels you choose? SunPower has been a leader in solar for more than 30 years.


· How reliable are the panels you choose? Independent tests prove SunPower panels are unmatched[1] and SunPower predicts its panels will have a useful life of more than 40 years[2].


· Finally, be sure to talk to your SunPower Partner about the benefits and flexibility of the financing options available to you.


Thank you again for your interest in the best solar solution under the sun.

Warmly,

The SunPower Team
1-800-SUNPOWER

1. #1 rank in &quot;Fraunhofer PV Durability Initiative for Solar Modules: Part 2&quot;. Photovoltaics International, 2014. Campeau, Z. et al. &quot;SunPower Module Degradation Rate,&quot; SunPower white paper, 2013. See www.sunpowercorp.com/facts for details.


2. &quot;SunPower Module 40-Year Useful Life,&quot; SunPower white paper. Feb 2013. Useful life is 99 out of 100 panels operating at more than 70% of rated power.



We do not share your information outside of SunPower and your Dealer Partner.

Privacy Statement

© 2015 SunPower Corporation. All Rights Reserved. SUNPOWER and the SUNPOWER logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of SunPower Corporation in the U.S. and other countries.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
