<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Unassigned Leads - Intro email to HO</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>SunPower_Lead_Gen_Letterhead_Template2</letterhead>
    <name>Unassigned Leads - HO email - Meet your SunPower Partner</name>
    <style>formalLetter</style>
    <subject>{!Opportunity.Account}, Meet Your SunPower Partner</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Opportunity.Account},


Good news! We’re happy to let you know that we’ve identified a highly-qualified SunPower® partner to provide the perfect solar solution for your needs.


While we regret that your home was beyond our coverage area when you originally requested information, we haven’t forgotten about you! We’re pleased that our steady growth now makes it possible to serve you and your neighbors.


Allow us to introduce you to your SunPower Partner:

{!Opportunity.Partner_Account_text__c}

{!Opportunity.Partner_Phone__c}


{!Opportunity.Partner_Account_text__c} will contact you within 2 days, or you can call them at your convenience.



When making a decision about solar, there are a few key things to keep in mind:

Preparing for your meeting: Gather as many of your electric bills as you can from the past 12 months. Don’t have your old bills handy? Don’t worry, most utilities allow you to download the previous year’s bill. This will help to accurately calculate your current usage.
How dependable is the company behind the panels you choose? SunPower has been a leader in solar for more than 30 years.
How reliable are the panels you choose? Independent tests prove SunPower panels are unmatched[1] and SunPower predicts its panels will have a useful life of more than 40 years[2].
Will my solar panels produce a lot of energy? SunPower solar panels produce way more power than conventional ones. About 75% more over the first 25 years! So it takes fewer panels on your roof to make the same amount of power.
Finally, be sure to talk to your SunPower Partner about the benefits and flexibility of the financing options available to you.



Thank you again for your interest in the best solar solution under the sun. If you have any questions, please call 1-800-SUNPOWER or email us at customersupport@sunpowercorp.com.



Looking forward to your joining us in changing the way the world is powered,



&lt;Name&gt;

SunPower Customer Support Team

www.sunpowercorp.com


1800-SUNPOWER

Disclaimers:

1. #1 rank in &quot;PV Module Durability Initiative Public Report,&quot; Fraunhofer ISE, Feb 2013. Five out of the top 8 largest manufacturers were tested. Campeau, Z. et al. &quot;SunPower Module Degradation Rate,&quot; SunPower white paper, Feb 2013. See www.sunpowercorp.com/facts for details.

2. &quot;SunPower Module 40-Year Useful Life,&quot; SunPower white paper. Feb 2013. Useful life is 99 out of 100 panels operating at more than 70% of rated power.


We do not share your information outside of SunPower and your Dealer Partner. Privacy Statement



© 2015 SunPower Corporation.  All Rights Reserved.  SUNPOWER and the SUNPOWER logo are trademarks or registered trademarks of SunPower Corporation in the U.S. and other countries as well.</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
